

VITALI MAXIMOV

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Professional with more than 15 years of experience in marketing and advertising field, with strong background in the entire printing production life cycle. Open minded, passionate about technology and latest trends. Ready to explore a career opportunity in IT. Quick learner, up for new challenges, adaptable and flexible.

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile: +37379017560

E-mail: shoken.mv@gmail.com Address: Str. M.Basarab, 2, ap.91,

mun. Chisinau, MD-2068

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Managed to optimize processes in the companies and new machines installation;
- Managed a team of 6 person;
- Fast learner.

COMPETENCIES

- Customer focus;
- Good communication;
- Flexibility;
- Organizational skills;
- Good listener;
- Solution oriented.

KNOWLEDGE

- Advertising industry market;
- Excellent knowledge of equipment and production process in the advertising field;
- Graphics;
- Team management up to 6 people;
- Projection and implementation.

LANGUAGES

- Romanian Elementary;
- English Intermediate (B1.1);
- Bulgarian fluent;
- Russian mother tongue.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Windows OS, Linux OS
- Office
- SOI
- Basics of HTML, CSS
- Corel Draw, Adobe Photoshop
- Compass 3D, AutoCad

ADDITIONAL COURSES

- English courses

 Quo vadis | April 2019 ongoing
- Software testing courses
 I and II parts
 SkillUp | July 2019
- Web Development.
 Введение в FrontEnd разработку
 Universarium.org | June 2020

CAREER HISTORY

Production Engineer

Maican-com SRL | May 2016 – October 2019

- Developing production and printing process;
- Acquisition of materials and price negotiation;
- Establishing budget and campaign management;
- Project owner of the online store maicom.com (MD and RO).

Production Engineer

Mediastil Grup SRL | May 2011 – April 2016

- · Price strategy and analysis;
- Organization of the production process;
- Business development;
- Client relationship and service;
- Responsible of company's production assets and inventory.

Chief of Production

Promo Studio SRL | August 2009 – October 2010

- Ensured that production is costeffective;
- Estimation of cost and quality standards;
- Monitored production and implemented quality control;
- Supervised and motivated my team.

Production Engineer Manager

VARO-Inform SRL | January 2007 – July 2009

 Improved production efficiency by analyzing and planning work flow;

- Kept equipment operational;
- Developed production processes by studying product requirements: researching, designing, modifying, and testing production methods and equipment.

Engineer, Advertising Production

Art-Vega SRL | March 2006 – January 2007

- Pre-Press process coordination;
- Organized and developed production process;
- · Communication with suppliers;

Pressman

Luxochim SRL | September 2005 – March 2006

- Pre-press;
- · Equipment adjustment;
- Supervising the printing process.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

- Moldova State University Faculty of Economics.
 Year 2009
- Tiraspol State University
 Faculty of Science in Engineering.
 Year 2004